nbadraft.net 2003-06-21

# NBADraft.net - Privacy Policy

##  _Privacy Statement for NBA Draft.net_

**NBA Draft.net** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [ NBA Draft.net ](http://nbadraft.net/)

####  Information Automatically Logged 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information.

####  Cookies 

Our Site uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. __

####  Advertisers 

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

Some customer data is shared with the advertising companies. 

####  Personal Information 

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. 

Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes. 

####  External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **NBA Draft.net** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

####  Public Forums 

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

##  Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:   

_[nbadraftnet@yahoo.com](mailto:nbadraftnet@yahoo.com)_

Copyright © 2000 NBADraft.net All rights reserved.
